Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Roy Glah papers, 1947-2003 and undated RL.00704
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Print Material, 1947-2000 and undated; 4
  - Association of National Advertisers--Event Marketing: A Management Guide, 1995 (Box 40)
  - The Berkeley Hotel (London), 1997 (Box 40)
  - Brains + Clout = Results, undated (Box 40)
  - Branding Ideas, 1997 (Box 40)
  - British American Chamber of Commerce publications, 1997-1998 (Box 40)
  - Brown's Hotel (London), 1997 (Box 40)
  - The Business of Imagination, The Art of Creating Convictions, 1998 (Box 40)
  - Cannes Lions publications, 1997 (Box 40)
  - Change/Inter Change (newsletter), 1995 (Box 40)
  - Coca-Cola: Our Company, 1996 (Box 41)
  - Combating Private Labels in the 1990s, circa 1993 (Box 41)
  - Engage (Enterprise Creative Selling), 1998 (Box 41)
  - Fortune Magazine: article on JWT, 1947 (Box 41)
  - Fortune Magazine: J. Walter Thompson is Alive and Well in 30 Countries, 1970 (Box 41)
  - Frohlinger Advertising Forecast, 1994 (Box 41)
  - Frohlinger Consensus Marketing Forecast Guide, 1995-1997; 3 folders (Box 41)
  - Frohlinger Marketing Report, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Frohlinger Marketing Report, 1995-1997; 3 folders (Box 42)
  - Global Business Report, 1999 (Box 42)
  - Global Resource Assessment, 1998 (Box 42)
  - The High Wire (JWT Specialised Communications), 1997 (Box 42)
  - Hindustan Thompson: HTA Today, 1994 (Box 42)
  - IMG (Information Marketing Group): The New Communications Agency, 1999 (Box 42)
  - Internal Brand Management, 1994 (Box 42)
  - J. Walter Merchandise catalog, 1994 (Box 42)
  - J. Walter Thompson: The Work/The Press, 2000 (Box 42)
  - J. Walter World, 1988 Dec. (Box 42)
  - JWT Account Team and Its Procedures, undated (Box 42)
  - JWT Change (newsletter), 1995-1996 (Box 42)
  - JWT credentials "One of the Great Worldwide Networks", 1997 (Box 42)
  - JWT Engine Room, undated (Box 42)
  - JWT New Business Checklist for Winners, 1992 (Box 42)
  - JWT Whitpaper: Combating Private Labels in the 1990s, 1993 (Box 43)
  - JWT Yearbook: It's a Wonderful Life, 1994 (Box 43)
  - Larry Light/Richard Morgan: Brand Loyalty Marketing, 1994 (Box 43)
  - Le Commodore (newsletter), 1994 (Box 43)
  - Looking Up at JWT, 1992 (Box 43)
  - Louis Harris: Advertising Agency Reputation Survey, 1989 (Box 43)
  - Maister Associates: JWT Materials for Discussion, 1996 (Box 43)
  - The Many Worlds of Sam Meek, 1981 (Box 43)
  - Media: The New Creative Frontier?, 1989 (Box 43)
  - Media, Consumers, and Commercial Communications (England), 1998 (Box 43)
  - Multinational Accounts as a Source of New Business, 1991 (Box 43)
  - National Sales Hall of Fame (Burt Manning induction), 1995 (Box 43)
  - New Business Services, undated (Box 43)
  - Odyssey of the Commodore, undated (Box 43)
  - Opinion Research Corporation--Winning Business Drivers: A Study on Building a Business-to-Business Brand, 1998 (Box 43)
  - Runnymede Hotel (Surrey, England), 1997 (Box 43)
  - Salz Survey of Advertiser-Agency Relations, 1992 (Box 43)
  - Smith Clark: Summary Analysis of the Leadership Aptitude and Practices Survey (LAPS) Results, 1994 (Box 44)
  - Smith Clark: The Thompson Way of Managing an Office, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Sprint Advertising Collection in the JWT Archives at Duke University, 1998 (Box 44)
  - Sun Microsystems: Meet Network, 1995 (Box 44)
  - Superbrands: Brandweek Marketers of the Year, 1996 (Box 44)
  - The Talent of Our People: A Selection of Human Resources Materials from the JWT Archives at Duke University (Box 44)
  - The Thompson Way, 1997 (Box 44)
  - Thompson Connect: Where Do We Want to Go Today?, circa 1999 (Box 44)
  - Thompson Total Branding booklets, 1997 (Box 44)
  - Thompson Total Branding Guidebook, 1997 (Box 44)
  - Total Compensation Program for John Q. Example, 1994 (Box 44)
  - Transformation, circa 1995 (Box 44)
  - Turnberry Isle Resort, undated (Box 65)
  - Who Will Lead the Thompson Company in the Year 2000?, 1985 (Box 44)
  - World Partners Council handout--Castello Marchesi Longhi de Paolis (English, Italian, German, French), undated (Box 44)
  - World Partners Council handout--Marco Cianchi: Leonardo da Vinci's Machines, 1988 (Box 44)
- Speeches, Writings, Presentations, 1978-1999 and undated; 5
  - General, 1978-1999 and undated; 5
    - 1990 and Beyond (Box 44)
    - 2000 and Beyond: The New Golden Age of Creativity? (With slides), 1997; 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Alan Goltz: J. Walter Kids, 1994 (Box 44)
    - American Lifestages, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Andy Fenning--Globalization, 1996 (Box 45)
    - Andy Fenning--Proposal for the first of a quarterly update to be sent to World Partners starting next week, 1996 (Box 45)
    - Andy Fenning--Thompson Total Branding Knowledge Sharing, 1997 (Box 45)
    - Arny Langbo--Advertising discussion, 1998 (Box 45)
    - Bernard Owett--Beyond Trendiness: The Search for the New, 1994 (Box 45)
    - Bill Thompson--Strategic Plan, 1994 (Box 45)
    - Bill Thompson--Unilever Directors, 1993 (Box 45)
    - Brian Johnson--Board of Directors, 1993 (Box 45)
    - Client-Focused Common Sense Approach to North American New Business, 1985 (Box 45)
    - Credentials presentation, undated (Box 45)
    - David Simpson--Importance of a Proper Client Brief, 1989 (Box 45)
    - DeBeers, 1992 (Box 45)
    - The Desensitization of America, undated (Box 45)
    - Digital @ JWT, 1999 (Box 45)
    - Don Johnston/John Sharman--Leadership at JWT, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Financial Analysts Meeting, 1993 (Box 45)
    - Global Branding: Myth or Reality?, 1989 (Box 45)
    - Grace Atkinson--Enter the Dragon, 1992 (Box 45)
    - Ideas for the Global Marketplace, 1996 (Box 46)
    - Institutional Investors (slides), 1994 (Box 46)
    - Ivan Arthur (Hindustan Thompson)--Quickly Run Upstairs and Write Me a Nice Hit Tune, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Jason Felton--Hong Kong and the Future, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Jim Foster--Media to the Max, 1996 (Box 46)
    - Joe O'Donnell--The Expectations of Our People, 1984 (Box 46)
    - John Holmes--Latin America, 1996 (Box 46)
    - JWT Consumer Panel and Village, 1987 (Box 46)
    - JWT Creative Standards, 1997 (Box 46)
    - JWT Credentials, 1991 (Box 46)
    - JWT Credentials--What Separates Us from Other Agencies?, 1989 (Box 46)
    - JWT Lever Division Bangkok, 1994 (Box 46)
    - JWT South East Asia Review, 1997 (Box 46)
    - JWT USA Financial Planning, 1990 (Box 46)
    - JWT Vietnam--Total Communications Solutions, 1995 (Box 46)
    - Kodak: The Picture Is Changing, 1996 (Box 46)
    - Latin America Region, 1996 (Box 46)
    - Lew Trencher--Asia Pacific Managers Meeting, 1993 (Box 47)
    - Lew Trencher--WPP Analysts Meeting, 1996 (Box 47)
    - Lloyd Stein--Getting More Out of Your Agency, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Management Contact and Quality Control, 1990 (Box 47)
    - Michael Perry--The Brand: Vehicle for Value in a Changing Marketplace, 1997 (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous speech materials: "Change", 1993 (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous speech materials: "Future", 1990-1992 (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous speech materials: "Likeability", 1991-1994; 3 folders (Box 47)
    - New Challenges for Advertising in Tomorrow's World, 1998 (Box 47)
    - Niall FitzGerald (Unilever)--Advertising for a Successful Europe, 1997 (Box 47)
    - Nina DiSesa--What Makes Great Advertising Work? (with slides), 1994; 3 folders (Box 47)
    - Peter Schweitzer--Asia Pacific trip, 1993 (Box 47)
    - Peter Schweitzer--It's a Small World, 1993 (Box 47)
    - Reference file, 1990 (Box 48)
    - Report on Progress of JWT Archives at Duke University, 1997 (Box 48)
    - Robin Restall--How to Get the Best from Your Advertising Agency, 1985 (Box 48)
    - Role of the Internet as a Marketing Medium, 1996 (Box 48)
    - Ron Burns--Human Resources, 1993 (Box 48)
    - Ron Burns--JWT USA Vital Signs, 1991 (Box 48)
    - Ron Burns--Leadership Through Innovation, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Ron Burns--New Business, 1992 (Box 48)
    - Ron Burns--So, What's the Big Idea?, 1994 (Box 48)
    - Ron Cromie--China: The Fragmenting Consumer Market, 1992 (Box 48)
    - Roy Glah--1992 A Banner Year, 1993 (Box 48)
    - Roy Glah--Financial Analysts Meeting, 1994 (Box 48)
    - Roy Glah--Human Resources Conference, 1993 (Box 49)
    - Shelly Lazarus--Positioning the Agency as a Brand, 1997 (Box 49)
    - Staff speech (slides), 1995 (Box 49)
    - Steve Davis--Mid-Summer, 1995 (Box 49)
    - Successfully Managing Change, 1986 (Box 49)
    - Thompson Way of Total Branding, 1996 (Box 49)
    - What Makes Great Advertising Work? (Abruption), with slides, 1993; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Wolfgang Berndt (Procter & Gamble)--Clean Slate: Lessons About Brand Building, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Burt Manning, 1988-1997 and undated; 6
    - 25th Anniversary, 1993 (Box 49)
    - 1992 A Banner Year for JWT, 1993 (Box 49)
    - AAAA Acceptance, 1995 (Box 49)
    - AAAA Chairman's Address, 1996 (Box 49)
    - Abruption, 1996 (Box 49)
    - Abruption--Binder, 1993 (Box 49)
    - Abruption--Chile, 1996 (Box 49)
    - Abruption--Correspondence and case studies, 1994; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Abruption in Coffee Advertising, 1995 (Box 50)
    - Abruption--Quality and Cost in Advertising, 1993 (Box 50)
    - Abruption--Santiago, 1996 (Box 50)
    - Abruption--Short version, 1996 (Box 50)
    - Abruption--Slides, 1993-1995; 4 folders (Box 50)
    - Acceptance remarks, AAF Silver Medal Award, 1996 (Box 50)
    - Ad Club of New York, 1991 (Box 50)
    - Advertising in the Internet Age, 1995; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Advertising's Future: TV or Not TV?, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Ambiguity of Client/Agency Relationships, 1995 (Box 51)
    - Asia Pacific Managers, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Board of Directors, 1992-1997; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Bottom Line on Brands (with slides), 1995; 4 folders (Box 51)
    - Branding of Emotion: How the Kodak Moment Was Born, 1996 (Box 51)
    - Closing Remarks, Board of Directors Meeting, 1996 (Box 51)
    - Creating Maximum Bandwidth, 1995 (Box 51)
    - Creating Maximum Bandwidth, 1995-1996; 3 folders (Box 52)
    - Creating Maximum Bandwidth--Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 52)
    - Creating Maximum Bandwidth--European tour, 1996 (Box 52)
    - Creating Maximum Bandwidth--Slides, 1995; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Creative Dissatisfaction, 1995 (Box 52)
    - DeBeers, 1991 (Box 52)
    - European General Managers Meeting, 1993 (Box 52)
    - European Managers Meeting, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Eyes on Thompson data file, 1989 (Box 53)
    - FCS Portfolio Awards Show, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Gatekeepers vs. Gate Crashers, 1991 (Box 53)
    - The Good, The Bad, and The World Wide Web (with slides), 1996; 5 folders (Box 53)
    - History of Kodak Advertising, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Institutional Investors Meeting, 1994 (Box 54)
    - Introduction of George Fisher (Kodak), 1996 (Box 54)
    - JWT London--1992 a Banner Year, 1993 (Box 54)
    - Key to Cost-Effective Advertising: Abruption, 1996 (Box 54)
    - Keynote, Club Circulo Creativo (Mexico), 1996 (Box 54)
    - Keynote, Unilever Awards, 1996 (Box 54)
    - Media: The New Creative Frontier?, 1989; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous slides, undated (Box 54)
    - Nestle meeting, 1993 (Box 54)
    - Neurobiology of Great Advertising: Abruption Cases (with slides), 1994; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - New Electronic Media (slides), 1995; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - New Electronic Media--Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 55)
    - New Electronic Media--Notes, undated; 3 folders (Box 55)
    - New Electronic Media: Dire Predictions and Hypothetical Threats, 1995 (Box 55)
    - An Optimistic Realistic Outlook on Chaos, 1992 (Box 55)
    - People, 1993 (Box 56)
    - Presentation for Mike Perry (Unilever), 1997 (Box 56)
    - Putting Your Brand on Sponsorships (with slides), 1995; 5 folders (Box 56)
    - Putting Your Brand on Sponsorships (reference clippings), 1995 (Box 66)
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising, 1993 (Box 56)
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--Abruption, 1993-1995; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--Abruption (Vienna), 1995 (Box 57)
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--Board of Directors version, 1993 (Box 57)
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--KGF Europe, 1994 (Box 57)
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--Vienna version (with slides), 1995; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - San Miguel pitch, 1995 (Box 57)
    - Seven Insoluble Agency Management Issues (with slides), 1995; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Speech notes, schedules, etc., 1995-1996 (Box 57)
    - Strategic Plan Progress Report, 1996 (Box 57)
    - Ten Insoluble Agency Management Issues (with slides), 1995; 4 folders (Box 58)
    - The Branding of Emotion: How the Kodak Moment Was Born, 1996 (Box 58)
    - The Soul of a Company, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Total Brand Communications, 1995 (Box 58)
    - Trends Affecting Products and People in the 2nd Half of the 90s, 1994 (Box 58)
    - Trends Affecting Products and People in the 2nd Half of the 90s--Reference file (with slides), 1994; 6 folders (Box 59)
    - Vampire Chronicles, undated (Box 59)
    - What Makes Great Advertising Work? (Abruption), 1994 (Box 59)
    - WPP Analysts Meeting, 1995 (Box 59)
    - WPP Board Meeting, 1991 (Box 60)
    - You Are Part of the Plan, 1996; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - You Are Part of the Plan--Asia Pacific, 1996; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - You Are Part of the Plan--Latin America, 1996 (Box 60)
    - You Are Part of the Plan--Slides, 1996; 3 folders (Box 60)
  - Burt Manning/Chris Jones, 1982-1996; 7
    - Duff and Phelps presentation, 1996 (Box 60)
    - Financial Analysts Meeting, 1996 (Box 61)
    - WPP Board Meeting, 1996; 3 folders (Box 61)
    - WPP Board Meeting--Acetates and notes, 1996 (Box 61)
    - WPP Board Meeting--Work file, 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - WPP General Meeting, 1996 (Box 62)
    - (With Peter Mills)--Managing the Agency, 1982 (Box 62)
  - Chris Jones, 1993-1999 and undated; 8
    - All India Management Association, 1996; 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Brand equity reference file, 1993-1996 (Box 62)
    - British American Chamber of Commerce, 1998; 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Creative Impact of Advertising, 1999 (Box 63)
    - Double Digit Profitability and Other Preoccupations, 1997; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Duke Leadership Training, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Englishman in New York, 1999; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - European School of Management, 1996; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Financial Analysts Meeting, 1997; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Ford Global Business Unit (GBU), 1997 (Box 63)
    - ICA (Toronto), 1996 (Box 63)
    - Ideas for the Global Marketplace, 1996 (Box 63)
    - Johns Hopkins School of Public Health, 1998 (Box 63)
    - Johns Hopkins, WACL reference file, 1997-1998 (Box 64)
    - JWT Mission Statement, 1998 (Box 64)
    - Kraft Conference, 1998 (Box 64)
    - Medill School of Journalism, 1996 (Box 64)
    - New Challenges for Advertising in Tomorrow's World, 1998 (Box 64)
    - Progress Report on the Transformation of JWT, 1999 (Box 64)
    - Rome speech, 1996 (Box 64)
    - Shell, 1996 (Box 64)
    - Should Advertising Be an Asset or a Debit on the Brand's Balance Sheet?, undated (Box 64)
    - Tomorrow's Marketing Today (with slides), 1998 (Box 64)
    - Unilever, 1998 (Box 64)
    - Uninvited Guest (with slides), 1999 (Box 64)
    - Women's Advertising Club of London (WACL), 1998 (Box 64)
    - World Partners, 1997 (Box 64)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1991-2001 and undated; 6
  - Videocassettes, 1991-2001 and undated; 9
    - Abruption Creative Reel, 1996 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-001)
      Includes Boddington Ale; Braethen Safe Air "Naked Lunch"; Bell Atlantic "Joanne"; French's Mustard; Smirnoff; Carte Noir Coffee; Polaroid; Honda; Volkswagen Passat launch
    - Abruption Project Reel 1, undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-002)
      22 spots: Nat West; Oxo; Timotei; Jaguar; Togs; Andrex; British Telecom; Polo; Persil; Kit Kat; De Beers; Golden Wonder Crisps; Lyon's Fab Ice Cream
    - Abruption Project Reel 2, 1993 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-003)
      9 spots: EPT; French's; Bell Atlantic; Burger King; Lubriderm; Ken'L Ration; California Lottery; Choclairs; Clorets
    - Abruption Project Reel 3, undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-004)
      5 spots: Oscar Mayer; Ford; Seven-Up; Kodak; Lever 2000
    - Abruption Project Reel 5, 1993 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-005)
      23 spots: 7-Eleven; Seven-Up; French's Mustard; Polo Mints; Kit Kat; Lubriderm; EPT; Ken'L Ration; Scott Andrex; Persil; Lyons Fab Ice Cream; Clorets; Timotei; California Lottery; De Beers; British Telecom; Bell Atlantic Caller ID; Pepsi; Continental Tires; Chanel; Magnavox; Whiskas; NYNEX Yellow Pages
    - Abruption reel for KGF, 1994 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-006)
      10 spots: California Lottery; 7-Eleven; French's Mustard; Bell Atlantic; Lunchables; Lubriderm; EPT; Pepsi Max; Lever 2000; Clorets; Kaiser Permanente; De Beers; Kodak
    - All India Management Association--Chris Jones speech materials, 1996 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-007)
      8 spots: Kraft Cheese; Unilever Drive; De Beers; Kellogg's Frosties; Oscar Mayer
    - Brand Connection Planning, 2000 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-008)
      Power of Conversation; A Magical Conversation (True Story); Kraft 4-:15; Marines 1999 TTB Award Video
    - Brand Summit, undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-009)
    - Brand Summit, undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-010)
    - Burt Manning Hall of Fame, 1999 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-011)
    - Burt Manning Inductio edit, 1999 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-012)
    - Burt Manning presentation, 1994 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-013)
      23 spots: 7-Eleven; French's Mustard; Bell Atlantic; Kit Kat; Schick; ESSO; Oscar Mayer Lunchables; Rolex; Timotei; Haagen Dazs; Ford; Lubriderm; Karwei; Lever 2000; Kellogg's Crunchy Nut; De Beers; Ken'L Ration; Greek Police; Kodak
    - Burt Manning presentation--Food prep final edit 3:06, undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-014)
    - Business of Imagination video 1:36, 1998 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-015)
    - Comparative Advertising, 1999 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-016)
      63 spots: Pepsi; Coke; Sprite; Burger King; McDonald's; Wendy's; Kraft Singles; Visa; American Express; Prego; Ragu; Avis; Dove; Pampers; Bounty; French's; Ford; Head & Shoulders
    - Competitive Comparative Advertising, 1999 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-017)
      27 spots: Ford; Allegheny; Pepsi/Coke; Burger King; McDonald's; Schlitz; Tylenol; Advil; Bayer; Energizer; Kraft; Pampers; Bounty; Dove; Visa; Wendy's; 7-Up; French's
    - Creating Impact in Advertising--Conference Board speech version 2, 1999 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-018)
    - The Creative Equation, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-019)
      20 spots: NYNEX; Pepsi; Timex; Continental Tires; Little Caesar's; Chanel; Nike; British Knights; Sinutab; Magnavox; Merrill Lynch; EPT; General Electric; Lever 2000; Chicken Tonight; Honda Prelude; Volkswagen; De Beers
    - Dell Branding Communications presentation (Mike Kalasunas), 1998 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-020)
    - Executive Group Meeting--New Creative from JWT Europe, 1999 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-021)
      25 spots: Portugal (Comissao Euro, Lactogal Calcio, Melhoral, TV Marcelo, Portugal Telecom, Banco Alimentar, Azeite Gallo); Spain (Trident, Kellogg's Corn Flakes); Italy (Telecom Italia Mobile, National Lottery); France (Lipton Ice); Sweden (Triss Lottery); UK London (Kit Kat, Dairylea Dunkers, Listerine); Netherlands (Tolerance Unlimited, Milupa, Heineken); Germany (Kronung, Siemens Gigaset); Austria (Generali)
    - Financial Analysts Meeting, 1993 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-022)
      16 spots: California Lottery; Clairol Ultress; Lever 2000; Jaguar; EPT; Bell Atlantic; Rolex; NOS Radio Station; Goodyear; Oscar Mayer Lunchables; De Beers; Sprint; Kodak; Chiclets; Ford
    - Food Advertising: Target Audience Parents, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-023)
    - Food edited clips for Burt Manning presentation, 1994 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-024)
    - Food titles A-G/San Francisco, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-025)
    - Food: Final RT 3:54, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-026)
    - Food one-on-one's A-E rough cut #1, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-027)
    - Food one-on-one's F-G part 2 plus San Francisco, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-028)
    - Ford, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-029)
    - Fran Engel: Working Woman, Forest Hills, Queens, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-030)
    - Francis Jackson: Working Woman, Forest Hills, Queens, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-031)
    - Gargerge International Showreel, 2000 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-032)
      9 spots: Spendrup's Original Beer; Folkhalsoinstitutet; ICA Organic Food; Viking Line; Carlshamn Mejeri Ice Cream; Diners Club; Poolia Temporary Employment Agency; Pharmacia + Upjohn
    - Institutional Investors presentation reel, 1994 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-033)
      11 spots: Rolex; Oscar Mayer Lunchables; De Beers; Chiclets; Ford Mustang; California Lottery; Gallo Olive Oil; Timotei; Toys R Us; Sprint; Kodak
    - JWT Chicago Approved TV Spots since July 1999 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-034)
      22 spots: Breakstone; Miracle Whip; Nabisco Triscuits; Heinz Wagwells; Nestle Butterfinger; Oscar Mayer Lunchables; Nabisco Ritz; Philly Snack Bars
    - JWT Europe final 6 months (television and print), 1999 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-035)
    - JWT Food Commercials, 1994 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-036)
    - JWT Food Commercials Reference, 1994 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-037)
    - JWT History Reel, undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-038)
      21 spots: Ford Mustang; Seven-Up; Pan Am; United States Marine Corps; Listerine; Kraft; Oscar Mayer; Aunt Jemima; Burger King; Orkin; French's; Samsonite; Sears Best Latex Paint; Schick; Kodak; Toys R Us
    - JWT International, 1999 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-039)
      12 spots: De Beers; Shell; Siemens; Kleen Bebe; Cordycepts; Christian Louboutin; Nestle; Kleenex; Kraft; Nike; Smirnoff
    - JWT London Showreel for Roy Glah, 1999 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-040)
      28 spots: Smirnoff; P&O Stena; Rolo; Shell; Polo; Dairylea Dunkers; Oxo; De Beers; Kit Kat; Boots Christmas; Persil; RNLI
    - JWT Media Directors Conference 12:00, 1996 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-041)
    - JWT Television Commercials, 1999 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-042)
      44 spots: Ford; Kraft; Warner-Lambert; Unilever; Nestle; Shell; Kellogg; Merrill Lynch; Siemens; Tim Horton's; Kleen Bebe; Cordycepts; Phoenix; Bayer; Christian Louboutin; Royal Air Force; United States Marine Corps; Qwest; Blockbuster; Dairylea Dunker; Sunsweet; De Beers
    - JWT Venezuela Worldwide Board of Directors (Bobby Coimbra), circa 1996 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-043)
    - Latin America Presentation Reel, undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-044)
      22 spots: California Lottery; 7-Eleven; French's; Bell Atlantic; Kit Kat; Schick; ESSO; Timotei; Haagen Dazs; Ford; Lubriderm; Chiclets; Lever 2000; De Beers; Ken'L Ration; Kodak
    - North America Managers Meeting, 1999 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-045)
      33 spots: Slazenger; Orkin; Maxfli; Kraft; Lever 2000; Kellogg's; Thermasilk; Blockbuster; Nabisco; Claussen; Miracle Whip; Ford; White Castle; Merrill Lynch; Qwest; Lipton; Sunsweet; UDV (BV Wines)